export const questions = [
  {
    question: "Which team won the Champions League in the season 2023/2024?",
    choice1: "Atalanta",
    choice2: "Bayer Leverkusen",
    choice3: "Borussia Dortmund",
    choice4: "Real Madrid",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which team has won the most World Cups?",
    choice1: "Argentina",
    choice2: "Brazil",
    choice3: "France",
    choice4: "Spain",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "When did the World Cup start?",
    choice1: "1928",
    choice2: "1929",
    choice3: "1930",
    choice4: "1931",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the only Swedish club that won the Champions League?",
    choice1: "Goteborg",
    choice2: "Linkoping",
    choice3: "Malmo",
    choice4: "Stockholm",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Where is Mehdi Taremi from?",
    choice1: "Iran",
    choice2: "Morocco",
    choice3: "Qatar",
    choice4: "Saudi Arabia",
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player was a legend at Barcelona, then moved to PSG and lastly to Inter Miami?",
    choice1: "Sergio Busquets",
    choice2: "Neymar Jr.",
    choice3: "Jordi Alba",
    choice4: "Lionel Messi",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "How many Ballon d'Ors does Ronaldo have?",
    choice1: "4",
    choice2: "5",
    choice3: "6",
    choice4: "7",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which anime is about Football?",
    choice1: "Bleach",
    choice2: "Solo Levelling",
    choice3: "Blue Lock",
    choice4: "Haikyuu",
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the only goalkeeper that has won the Ballon D'Or?",
    choice1: "Gianluigi Donnarumma",
    choice2: "Lev Yashin",
    choice3: "Petr Cech",
    choice4: "Gianluigi Buffon",
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which club went unbeaten in 2023/2024 in the Bundesliga?",
    choice1: "VfB Stuttgart",
    choice2: "Bayern Munchen",
    choice3: "Borussia Dortmund",
    choice4: "Bayer Leverkusen",
    answer: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "Which 2 teams were in the 2024/2025 Champions League final?",
    choice1: "PSG and Barcelona ",
    choice2: "Bayern Munchen and PSG",
    choice3: "Inter Milan and Barcelona",
    choice4: "PSG and Inter Milan",
    answer: 4,
  },
];
